At the time of this recording,
在录制这个视频时
Spark's latest release version 2.2.1
Spark 的最新版本 2.2.1
supports two machine learning libraries,
同时支持两个机器学习库
Spark ML and Spark MLlib.
Spark ML 和 Spark MLlib
Spark MLlib is an additive base library
Spark MLlib 是一个基于 RDD 的库
and it has been in maintenance board since version 2.2.
它自2.2版开始已进入维护模式
According to the current plans,
根据目前的规划
Spark ML, the DataFrames API,
Spark ML 即基于 DataFrames 的 API
will be feature complete by version 2.3,
的功能将在2.3版本中得到完善
and then the order Spark MLlib will be removed in Spark 3.2.
在这之后 Spark MLlib 将从 Spark 3.0 中删除
So currently, we might need to use a mixture of these two libraries,
所以目前 我们会混搭着使用这两个库
but as time goes on,
但之后
you should focus on Spark ML,
因为 Spark ML 会慢慢变成 Spark 的标准机器学习库
as It's becoming Sparks standard machine learning library.
所以你要把重心放在这个库上
Just as Spark DataFrames were designed closely
就像 Spark DataFrames 的设计和
mimicking Python and R DataFrames,
Python 以及 R 的 DataFrames 很像
the Spark ML library resembles Scikit-learn.
Spark ML 库设计的和 Scikit-learn 很像
It supports pipelines where we can stitch together data
它提供的管道可以让我们把数据清洗
cleaning and feature engineering steps with moral training and prediction.
特征工程的步骤和模型训练以及预测缝合在一起
Spark in general, handles algorithms that scale linearly with the input data size.
通常来讲 Spark 提供用来处理与输入数据大小成线性比例的算法的支持
In the library, we find support for the most common
在库里 可以找到对最常见
linear algorithms such as linear and logistic regression,
线性算法的支持 如线性和逻辑回归
Random Forest and k-means clustering.
随机森林和 k 均值聚类
Spark ML also has utilities for feature computation,
Spark ML 还有用于特征计算
hyperparameter tuning, and model evaluation.
调参和模型评估的工具
Then we think about Distributed Machine Learning,
然后我们想到分布式机器学习
there are two different ways to achieve parallelization,
有两种不同的方法可以实现并行化
data parallelization, and task parallelization.
数据并行化和任务并行化
We can use a large dataset and train
我们可以使用大型数据集
the same model on smaller subsets of the data in parallel.
以并行的方式把同一模型放在数据集的子集上进行训练
This is bugs before behavior.
这是 Spark 之前的处理方式。
The Driver Program acts as a perimeter server for
DAG 程序会充当
most algorithms where the partial results of each iteration gets combined.
大多数算法的服务器，每个部分结果的迭代会被汇总
We can also think about training many models in
我们也可以同时在多台机器上并行训练模型
parallel on a dataset small enough to fit on a single machine.
每份数据集足以塞进一台机器
We will cover Spark's current and future options on tuning
我们将在超参数调优部分介绍Spark目前和以后
models in parallel in the section about hyperparameter tuning.
并行训练模型的选项